Finding Aid for the Delbert Mann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Productions
  - Productions Directed by Others
    - The Last Tycoon, 16 October 1949; Script Cast List (Box 80)
    - The Unforgiven, 1957 (Released 1960); Script Casting Notes Notes (Box 80)
    - A Fine Madness, 1964 (Released 1966); Script Report Production Proposal Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photographs Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Schedule Set List Sketches Location List Photograph List Budget Correspondence (Box 80)
    - A Fine Madness, 1964 (Released 1966); Script Report Production Proposal Scripts Cast Lists Casting Photographs Notes Background Scene and Actor Breakdown Schedule Set List Sketches Location List Photograph List Budget Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Doctor, You’ve Got to Be Kidding!, 1965-1966 (Released 1967); Scripts Casting Notes Notes Daily Production Reports Possible Set Deletions Budget Correspondence (Box 81)
    - Doctor, You’ve Got to Be Kidding!, 1965-1966 (Released 1967); Scripts Casting Notes Notes Daily Production Reports Possible Set Deletions Budget Correspondence (Box 82)
    - A Walk With Love and Death, 1964-1966 (Released 1969); Outlines Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Notes Background Scene and Set Breakdown Set Lists Sketches Location lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget Correspondence (Box 82)
    - A Walk With Love and Death, 1964-1966 (Released 1969); Outlines Scripts Casting Notes Casting Photographs Notes Background Scene and Set Breakdown Set Lists Sketches Location lists Location Information Location Photographs Budget Correspondence (Box 83)
    - The Beguiled, 1968 (Released 1971); Outline Casting Notes Correspondence (Box 84)
    - The Movies, 31 March-1 April 1974; Outlines Narrative Casting Notes Credits Cast Lists Producer Lists Director Lists Author Lists Film Lists Segment Descriptions Production Continuity Program Format Budget Publicity Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Kim, 1975; Scripts Casting Notes Notes Schedule Budget Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Say It Ain’t So, Joe, 1976-1979, 1986; Script Report Scripts Character Descriptions Cast Lists Notes Background Action Shots List Schedules Set List Set Breakdown Location Information Location Photographs Broadcast Standards Review Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Say It Ain’t So, Joe, 1976-1979, 1986; Script Report Scripts Character Descriptions Cast Lists Notes Background Action Shots List Schedules Set List Set Breakdown Location Information Location Photographs Broadcast Standards Review Correspondence (Box 85)
    - Squaring the Circle, 1982-1983; Scripts Notes Scene and Actor Breakdown Scene and Timing Breakdown Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Nabokov in Residence, 1984; Script Report Script Correspondence (Box 86)
    - The Old Man and the Sea, 1988 (Released 1989); Treatment Script Crew List Notes Schedule Sketches Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Incident at Bremen, 1989; Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Crew List Notes Set List Correspondence (Box 86)
    - Incident at Bremen, 1989; Script Report Scripts Script Revisions Crew List Notes Set List Correspondence (Box 87)
    - Two For the Seesaw, undated (Released 1962); Script (Box 87)
    - Fire On the Mountain, 1965, 1970 (Released 1981); Treatment Synopsis of Story Character Descriptions Casting Notes Notes Correspondence (Box 87)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (Box 87)
    - Outgoing (Box 87)
    - Incoming (Box 87)
    - Incoming (Box 88)
    - Incoming (Box 89)
    - SCRIPT REPORTS (Box 89)
    - 1960-1971 (Box 90)
    - 1972-1985 (Box 91)
    - 1986-1992 (Box 92)
    - WRITINGS, Memoirs: Looking Back, 5 volumes The War, Transition Part I – The Days When Television Was Live, 1949-1954 Part II – Mostly Feature Films, Plus Live Television, Some Theatre, and a Bit of Opera, 1954-1957 Part III – Films for Television, Plus Some Television On Tape, A Little Theatre, and a Feature Film or Two, 1967-1978 Part IV – More Films For Television, Plus Two Returns to Live Television and The Theatre, 1979-1992 Foreword, by Delbert Mann, to Writing for Film and Television, by Stewart Bronfeld (1981) “No Retakes,” Essay by Delbert Mann in How to Direct for Television, edited by William I. Kaufman (1955) (Box 92)
    - WRITINGS, Memoirs: Looking Back, 5 volumes The War, Transition Part I – The Days When Television Was Live, 1949-1954 Part II – Mostly Feature Films, Plus Live Television, Some Theatre, and a Bit of Opera, 1954-1957 Part III – Films for Television, Plus Some Television On Tape, A Little Theatre, and a Feature Film or Two, 1967-1978 Part IV – More Films For Television, Plus Two Returns to Live Television and The Theatre, 1979-1992 Foreword, by Delbert Mann, to Writing for Film and Television, by Stewart Bronfeld (1981) “No Retakes,” Essay by Delbert Mann in How to Direct for Television, edited by William I. Kaufman (1955) (Box 93)
    - WRITINGS, Memoirs: Looking Back, 5 volumes The War, Transition Part I – The Days When Television Was Live, 1949-1954 Part II – Mostly Feature Films, Plus Live Television, Some Theatre, and a Bit of Opera, 1954-1957 Part III – Films for Television, Plus Some Television On Tape, A Little Theatre, and a Feature Film or Two, 1967-1978 Part IV – More Films For Television, Plus Two Returns to Live Television and The Theatre, 1979-1992 Foreword, by Delbert Mann, to Writing for Film and Television, by Stewart Bronfeld (1981) “No Retakes,” Essay by Delbert Mann in How to Direct for Television, edited by William I. Kaufman (1955) (Box 94)
    - Biographical Information, Who’s Who Entries, Curriculum Vitae Columbia University, Oral History Interview, February 1959, Transcript Productions Directed by Delbert Mann Television Specials Directed by Delbert Mann Live Television Shows (Partial) and Theatre Productions Directed by Delbert Mann Theatrical Films Directed by Delbert Mann Actors’ Equity Association, Honorable Withdrawal Card, 1949 Legal Documents Regarding Delbert Mann’s Employment in Great Britain and Canada, 1969, 1987 Clippings (Box 95)
    - Articles, Davis, Louise. “Big Man on the Set,” The Nashville Tennessean Magazine, 11 September 1955 Davis, Louise. “The Star Makers: Two Nashvillians Produce TV’s Top Network Dramas,” The Nashville Tennessean Magazine, 4 September 1955 Russell, Steven. “Our Mann in Hollywood,” The Kaooa Alpha Journal, CVIII (Fall 1991), 8-10 (Box 95)
    - Academic Career, Vanderbilt University Yale Drama School Claremont Colleges, staff-Faculty Directory, 1974-1975 (showing Delbert Mann on faculty) (Box 95)
    - Honors and Awards, 303rd Army Air Forces Flying Training Detachment, Certificate for Completion of Pilot Training Course, 1943 491st Bombardment Group, United Kingdom, Certificate for Meritorious Service, 1945 American Foundation for the Blind, Certificate of Merit, ca. 1954 Directors Guild of America, Certificate, in Grateful Recognition of His Services as Member of the National Board, 1961-1963 The Film Daily, Filmdom’s Famous Fives, Certificate, 1955 Jack Daniel Distillery, Award of Tennessee Squire Title, Certificate, 1966 (Humorous) Kappa Alpha Scholarship Fund, Certificate of Life Membership, undated Motion Picture Herald in Association with Fame, Certificate, Award of Achievement as a Champion Director for 1954-55, New York, 1956 Motion Picture Herald in Association with Fame, Certificate, Award of Achievement as a Champion Director for 1962, New York, 1963 Northland College, Ashland, Wisconsin, Honorary Degree, Doctor of Laws, Certificate, 1959 The Southern California Motion Picture Council, Certificate, Bronze Halo Award, For Outstanding Contribution to the Entertainment Industry, 1984 The Southern California Motion Picture Council, Certificate, Golden Halo Award, for Love Leads the Way, 1984 United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. Council on Mass Media, Certificate of Appreciation, undated United States Air Force, Strategic Air Command, Certificate of Degree, B.S. (Bachelor of SACology), 1962 (Humorous) United States Army Air Forces, World War II, Certificate of Gratitude For Meritorious Service, [1945] USS Sea Fox, Certificate, Initiation as Honorary Crewmember, 1966 (Humorous) Yale University, Certificate of Gratitude, For Service as a Member of the Committee on the School of Drama of the University Council, 1960-1965 (Box 95)
    - Miscellaneous, Mickey Myers, Artist, Print inscribed to the Manns, 1983; biographical information on Myers (Box 95)
    - EVENTS AND ACTIVITIES, Academy of Television Arts & Sciences Tribute to Hume Cronyn and Jessica Tandy, 1 February 1989 Academy of Television Arts & Sciences Tribute to Angela Lansbury, 22 February 1990 Academy of Arts & Sciences Tribute to Delbert Mann, 1 March 1988 Elizabeth Allan--Clippings, 1952 American Cinema Editors Thirty-Eighth Eddie Awards Dinner, 19 March 1988 – Delbert Mann as presenter American Film Institute, Delbert Mann Retrospective, Summary Remarks, May 1972 Fred Coe Artist-In-Residence Fund, Vanderbilt University, Correspondence, 1984-1991 Fred Coe, Tribute, Tennessee Performing Arts Center, Opening, Nashville, 1980 Cork International Film Festival, Cork, Ireland, 1967 Emmy Awards, Programs, 1977-1978, 1979-1980 C. William Gibson, Jr., Cultural Symposium, Randolph-Macon College Cary Grant: Haunted Idol, by Geoffrey Wansell, 1983 – Delbert Mann quotes Hollywood: The Gift of Laughter, Documentary, 1981 Grace Kelly, Memorial Card, 1982 Penn State Invitational Film Festival, 1975 Francis Robinson Tribute Performance, Giuseppe Verdi’s Requiem Mass, Metropolitan Opera House, 20 February 1982 Saskatchewan Drama Association and the University of Saskatchewan High School Theatre Festival, 1981 The Search for Scarlett, October 1992 Vanderbilt University, Delbert Mann Film Festival, 1989 Virginia Conference on Television and Culture, 1978 Virginia Festival of American Film, 1988 (Box 95)
    - DIRECTORS GUILD OF AMERICA PAPERS, Correspondence, outgoing, 1967-1979 Correspondence, incoming, 1958-1984 Presidential Statements, Delbert Mann, 1968 Possessory Credits Dispute, Negotiations, 1967-1968 Possessory Credits Dispute, Agreements, Reports, 1967-1968 Possessory Credits Dispute, Press Coverage, 1967-1968 Violence in Film/Television, Press Coverage, 1968 (Box 96)
    - PRODUCTION COMPANIES, Trident Productions, 1963-1965, Correspondence Trident Productions, 1963-1965, Contract, Legal Papers Omnibus Productions Limited, 1970-1971, Correspondence Omnibus Productions Limited, 1970-1971, Philosophy, Script Summaries Proposed Production Company, 1974, Correspondence, Proposal (Box 96)
    - THEATRE AND OPERA COLLECTION (Box 97)
    - Ryman Auditorium, Proarams, Amphitryon 38, 7 March 1935 Blossom Time, 5 December 1935 Brother Rat, 31 January 1938 Carmen, 26 December 1934 (Signed by Dreda Aves and Olga Kargau) Cavalleria Rusticana, 27 December 1934 (Signed by several members of the cast) The Constant Wife, 27 October 1935 (Signed by Ethel Barrymore) Dodsworth, 11 March 1936 (Signed by Walter Huston and Nan Sunderland) Faust, 11 November 1938 (Signed by Franco Perulli, Nannette Guilford, Raymond Lutz, and Arthur Anderson) Golden Boy, 23 October 1939 Hansel and Gretel, 27 December 1934 (Signed by Charlotte Bruno and Maria Zara) Idiot’s Delight, 6 March 1939 (Signed by Alfred Lunt, Lynn Fontanne, Barry Thomson, Sydney Greenstreet, Richard Whorf, and Ralph Nelson) King Richard II, 18 January 1938 (Signed by Maurice Evans) Kiss the Boys Goodbye, 28 March (ca.) 1941 Life With Father, 6 January (ca.) 1941 The Little Foxes, 18 February 1941 The Man Who Came to Dinner, 10 February 1941 (Signed by Clifton Webb) Mary of Scotland, 30 March 1935 (Signed by Helen Hayes) My Dear Children, 21 April 1939 (Signed by John Barrymore, Philip Reed, Leo Chalzel, and Tala Birell) The Old Maid, 13 April (ca.) 1934 (Signed by Judith Anderson and Helen Menken) The Philadelphia Story, 21 January 1941 Romeo and Juliet, 16 December 1935 (Signed by Maurice Evans and Katharine Cornell) Skylark, 12 November 1940 (Signed by Gertrude Lawrence and John Emery) Springtime for Henry, 28 March 1940 (Signed by Edward Everett Horton) The Taming of the Shrew, 12 January 1940 (Signed by Alfred Lunt, Lynn Fontanne, Richard Whorf, Sydney Greenstreet, and Norman Stuart) There Shall Be No Night, 14 November 1941 Tobacco Road, 1 December 1938 (Signed by John Barton) Tovarich, 14 October 1937 (Signed by Eugenie Leontovich) Treat Her Gently, 25 April 1941 Victoria Regina, 30 March 1938 (Signed by Helen Hayes) Whiteoaks, 7 February 1939 (Signed by Ethel Barrymore) The Women, 27 December 1937 (Signed by Lois Wilson) Yes, My Darling Daughter, 7 March 1938 (Signed by Agnes Doyle, Florence Reed, and Lawrence Grossmith) (Box 97)
    - Metropolitan Opera, Programs, Aida, 1 January 1941 (Signed by Giovanni Martinelli) La Boheme, 3 January 1941 (Signed by Armand Tokatyau, Ezio Pinza, George Cehanovsky, and Jarmila Novotna) Norma, 29 October 1956 La Perichole, 21 December 1956 Tannhaeuser, 4 January 1941 (Signed by Lauritz Melchoi and Herbert Janssen) Die Walkure, 2 January 1941 (Signed by Erich Leinsdorf) (Box 97)
    - Ward-Belmont School, Programs, Charles Hackett Performance, 16 October 1934 (Signed by Charles Hackett) Frederick Jagel Performance, 16 April 1936 (Signed by Frederick Jagel) Charles Kullman Performance, 16 February 1937 (Signed by Charles Kullman) Kathryn Meisle Performance, 14 October 1935 (Signed by Kathryn Meisle) (Box 97)
    - Community Concert Association, Programs, Henri Deering Performance, ca. 1940 (Signed by Henri Deering) Lotte Lehmann Performance, ca. 1940 (Signed by Lotte Lehmann) Philadelphia Orchestra with Eugene Ormandy, ca. 1940 (Signed by Eugene Ormandy) (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous Theatre and Opera Proarams, Auditorium Theatre, Chicago – Macbeth, 1928 The Avon Players – The Merchant of Venice The Avon Players – Othello, Hamlet The Ben Greet Players – Julius caesar, Macbeth, Hamlet, The Comedy of Errors, Twelfth Night, As You Like It Booth Theatre, New York – The Playboy of the Western World Cornell, Katharine – Antony and Cleopatra Evans, Maurice – Hamlet, ca. 1946 Harris Theatre, Chicago – You Can’t Take It With You Kazan, Elia – A Streetcar Named Desire Municipal Auditorium – Porgy and Bess, 11 December 1943 New York City Opera Company – He Who Gets Slapped, 12 April 1959 Peabody College Hillsboro Players – The Late Christopher Bean, directed by Frederick Coe The Playbill, Empire Theatre, New York – Life With Father, 1940 The Playbill, Guild Theatre, New York – Flight to the West, 1940 The Playbill, National Theatre, New York – The Corn is Green, 1940 The Playbill, St. James Theatre, New York – Twelfth Night, 1940 The Playwrights’ Company – Joan of Lorraine The Playwrights’ Company and the Theatre Guild – There Shall Be No Night, with Alfred Lunt and Lynn Fontanne The Messrs. Shubert – Dark of the Moon The Theatre Guild – O Mistress Mine, with Alfred Lunt and Lynn Fontanne, ca. 1946 The Theatre Guild – Oklahoma! The Theatre Guild – Twelfth Night Aida, 23 August 1936 (Signed by several members of the cast) Annie, Get Your Gun, with Ethel Merman Blithe Spirit Carmen Jones Carousel Cyrano de Bergerac Medea Porgy and Bess Show Boat The Tempest You Can’t Take It With You Cincinnati Summer Opera, Program, 1936 Metropolitan Amusement Guide, 1924; War Memorial Auditorium Recital, Ticket, 1937 (Box 97)
    - Motion Picture Souvenir Programs, Henry V, Laurence Olivier A Midsummer Night’s Dream, Warner Brothers Richard III, Laurence Olivier Romeo and Juliet, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer The Tales of Hoffman, London Films (Box 97)
    - PHOTOGRAPHS, Allan, Elizabeth Allan, Elizabeth in David Copperfield, 1935. Inscribed and signed. Allan, Elizabeth in A Tale of Two Cities. Inscribed and signed, 1945. Allan, Elizabeth and Ronald Colman in A Tale of Two Cities Arlen, Richard. Inscribed and signed. Bailey, Pearl in The Member of the Wedding. Inscribed and signed. Barnard, Henry. Inscribed and signed. Barrymore, Ethel. Inscribed and signed, 1945. Bartholomew, Freddie, Elizabeth Allan, Basil Rathbone, Violet Kemble-Copper in David Copperfield, 1935. Bennett, Joan. Inscribed and signed. Borgnine, Ernest. Inscribed and signed. Bragger, Fred. Inscribed and signed. Claire, Ina, Norman Stuart, Arnold Korff in The Theatre Guild Production of Biography Constantine, Michael, in Quick, Before It Melts Cowl, Jane. Inscribed and signed. Crawford, Ann. Inscribed and signed. Curtis, Tony in The Outsider. Inscribed and signed. Cusack, Cyril in David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Cusack, Sinead in David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Daley, Jan. Inscribed and signed. Day, Doris. Inscribed and signed. Desmond, Johnny and Joey Adams in Play Me Hearts and Flowers. Inscribed and signed, 1955. Dunn, Jimmy. Inscribed and signed. Ebsen, Buddy. Inscribed and signed. Evans, Edith in David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Evans, Madge. Inscribed and signed. Evans, Maurice in Richard II. Inscribed and signed. Field, Sylvia. Inscribed and signed. Fort, Hank. Inscribed and signed. Franklin, Pamela in David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Gray, Glen. Inscribed and signed. Hayworth, Rita and Deborah Kerr in Separate Tables Hillaire, Marcel. Inscribed and signed. Hopper, Hedda. Inscribed and signed. Hopper, Hedda, Delbert Mann, and Anthony Perkins. Inscribed and signed by Hedda Hopper. Hunt, Bradford. Inscribed and signed. Jurgens, Dick. Inscribed and signed. Kellin, Mike. Signed. Kelly, Grace (three photographs) Kerr, Deborah and Gladys Cooper in Separate Tables Kerr, Deborah and David Niven in Separate Tables Kool, Harry. Inscribed and signed. Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne in Idiot’s Delight, 1936. Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne in Reunion in Vienna, 1931. Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne in The Taming of the Shrew. Lytell, Bert. Inscribed and signed. McCarthy, Frank. Inscribed and signed, 1978. Maharis, George in Quick, Before It Melts. Mann, Delbert and cast in The Outsider. Inscribed and signed by Tony Curtis. Martinelli, Giovanni. Inscribed and signed, 1935. Massey, Raymond and Charles Laughton in The Day Lincoln Was Shot, 1956. Inscribed and signed by Massey. Morse, Robert in Quick, Before It Melts Niven, David. Inscribed and signed. Niven, David in Separate Tables Niven, David and Deborah Kerr in Separate Tables (2 photographs) Niven, David and Norman Stuart. Inscribed and signed. Ormandy, Eugene. Signed. Phillips, Robin in David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Phillips, Robin as David Copperfield. Inscribed and signed. Pilbeam, Nova. Inscribed and signed. Raeburn, Boyd. Inscribed and signed. Romburg, Sigmund. Inscribed and signed. Savitt, Jan. Inscribed and signed. Sterling, Robert. Inscribed and signed. Stueckgold, Grete. Inscribed and signed. Truex, Ernest. Inscribed and signed. Van Patten, Joyce. Inscribed and signed. Vidor, King. Inscribed and signed, 1935. Weicker, Lowell. Signed. Wells, Selman. Inscribed and signed. Wilson, Lois and Eddie Nugent. Inscribed and signed. Wood, Peggy. Inscribed and signed. Yale Drama School (Luis Martinez, Julia Meade, Frank Corsaro, Unidentified, Bob Costello, J.P. Miller). Signed by Julia Meade and J.P. Miller. (Box 98)
    - PHOTOGRAPHS (Photocopies) (Box 99)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front, 1979 (4), Ernest Borgnine, Richard Thomas Ernest Borgnine, Richard Thomas Denys Graham (Kaiser Wilhelm) Village under attack (Box 99)
    - April Morning, 1987 (4), Delbert Mann, Susan Blakely Delbert Mann Delbert Mann, Ken Siegel (Box 99)
    - The Bachelor Party, 1956 (2), Philip Abbott, Jack Warden, Don Murray, E.G. Marshall Don Murray, Carolyn Jones (Box 99)
    - Birch Interval, 1974; Manny Metaxis, Delbert Mann, Urs Ferrer, Susan McClung (Box 99)
    - Breaking Up, 1976; Lee Remick (Box 99)
    - Bronte, 1982 (2), Julie Harris Julie Harris, Delbert Mann (Box 99)
    - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1960 (3), Dorothy McGuire, Jack Warner, Delbert Mann, Robert Preston Delbert Mann, Dorothy McGuire, William Inge, Robert Preston, Michael Garrison Bobby Eyer, Lee Kinsolving, Robert Preston, Dorothy McGuire, Shirley Knight, Eve Arden (Box 99)
    - Darkness at Noon, 1955 (2), Lee J. Cobb, Oscar Homolka Prison Cells set (Box 99)
    - David Copperfield, 1970 (6), Alistaire Mackenzie, Richard Attenborough, Laurence Olivier Richard Attenborough, Laurence Olivier Wendy Hiller Delbert Mann, Ralph Richardson Dominic Fulford, Delbert Mann Delbert Mann, Charlton Heston, Laurence Olivier (Box 99)
    - The Day Lincoln Was Shot, 1956 (3), Bill Holbrook, Delbert Mann, Raymond Massey, Charles Laughton, Jack Lemmon Lillian Gish, Raymond Massey Jack Lemmon (Box 99)
    - Dear Heart, 1963 (3), Patricia Barry, Glenn Ford, Geraldine Page Delbert Mann, Frank Stanley Geraldine Page, Delbert Mann, Glenn Ford (Penn Station, New York) (Box 99)
    - A Death in California, 1985; Sam Elliott, Cheryl Ladd (Box 99)
    - Desire Under the Elms, 1957 (4), Sophia Loren, Delbert Mann Sophia Loren, Delbert Mann Sophia Loren, Delbert Mann, Anthony Perkins, Burl Ives Dick Elliott, Burl Ives, Jean Willes, Rebecca Wells (Box 99)
    - Dusty Portrait, 1952; Sumner Locke Elliott, Fred Coe, Delbert Mann (Box 99)
    - Elegy, 1953; Charlton Heston, William Prince (Box 99)
    - The First Woman President, 1974; Eva Marie Saint, Richard Basehart (Box 99)
    - Fitzwilly, 1966; Dick Van Dyke, Barbara Feldon Al Cline, Arthur Gerstle, Joe Biroc, Edith Evans, Dick Van Dyke, Barbara Feldon Anthony Enstrel, Noam Pitlik, Dick Van Dyke, Nelson Olmsted, Sam Waterston, Lew Brown, Delbert Mann, Helen Kleeb, Edith Evans, Karen Norris, Patience Cleveland, Albert Carrier, Barbara Feldon (Box 99)
    - A Gathering of Eagles, 1962 (5), Rock Hudson Beale Air Force Base, Marysville, California Foster Rhinney, Richard Anderson, Rock Hudson, Delbert Mann Curtis LeMay, Ann Mann, Mrs. Curtis LeMay, Delbert Mann (Box 99)
    - The Gift of Love, 1983 (2), Lee Remick Angela Lansbury, Lee Remick (Box 99)
    - A Girl Named Sooner, 1974; Delbert Mann, Lee Remick (Box 99)
    - Heidi, 1967 (3), Maximilian Schell, Jennifer Edwards, Jean Simmons Maximilian Schell, Jennifer Edwards Michael Redgrave, Jennifer Edwards (Box 99)
    - Home to Stay, 1977 (2), Henry Fonda, Michael McGuire Suzanne Clauser, Henry Fonda, Delbert Mann, Diana Kerew, Fred Bogger (Box 99)
    - Jane Eyre, 1970 (4), George C. Scott, Susannah York Delbert Mann, Susannah York, George C. Scott Susannah York Susannah York, George C. Scott (Box 99)
    - Kidnapped, 1971 (3), Peter Jeffrey, Jack Hawkins, Michael Caine Michael Caine, Freddie Jones Michael Caine (Box 99)
    - The Last Days of Patton, 1985 (4), Delbert Mann, George C. Scott Murray Hamilton, Delbert Mann, Del Acevedo, George C. Scott George C. Scott Delbert Mann, George C. Scott (Box 99)
    - Lee at Gettysburg, 1957; James Daly, William Smithers (Box 99)
    - Love Leads the Way, 1984 (2), Timothy Bottoms, “Buddy” Arthur Hill, Patricia Neal, Timothy Bottoms (Box 99)
    - Lover, Come Back, 1961 (3), Doris Day, Rock Hudson Jack Oakie, Edie Adams Rock Hudson (Box 99)
    - The Man Without a Country, 1973; Robert Ryan, Cliff Robertson (Box 99)
    - Marty, 1953; Nancy Marchand, Rod Steiger (Box 99)
    - Marty, 1954 (6), Ernest Borgnine, Betsy Blair Paddy Chayefsky, Harold Hecht, Delbert Mann Walter Kelly, Delbert Mann, Paddy Chayefsky, Ernest Borgnine Ernest Borgnine, Joe Mantell Billboard Director’s Screen Credit (Box 99)
    - The Member of the Wedding, 1982; Dana Hill, Pearl Bailey (Box 99)
    - Middle of the Night, 1959 (3), Fredric March, Kim Novak Delbert Mann, Kim Novak Fredric March, Kim Novak, Paddy Chayefsky, Delbert Mann (Box 99)
    - Mister Buddwing, 1964 (3), Jean Simmons, James Garner, Raymond St. Jacques, Rafael Campos James Garner, Angela Lansbury James Garner, Katharine Ross (Box 99)
    - Night Crossing, 1980 (3), Balloon Set (two photographs) John Hurt, Doug McKeon, Keith McKeon, Jane Alexander (Box 99)
    - October Story, 1951; Julie Harris (Box 99)